Shuffling the deck
cut at 39
cut at 22
cut at 33
cut at 37
cut at 38
cut at 37
cut at 38
Hand 1 bankroll 8
Player: Joseph Joestar bets 5
Player: Joseph Joestar dealt King of Spades
Dealer: Suzumiya Haruhi dealt Three of Diamonds
Player: Joseph Joestar dealt Six of Diamonds
Player: Joseph Joestar's total is 16
Dealer: Suzumiya Haruhi's hole card is Four of Spades
Dealer: Suzumiya Haruhi dealt Ten of Hearts
Dealer: Suzumiya Haruhi's total is 17
Dealer: Suzumiya Haruhi wins this hand
Player: Joseph Joestar has 3 after 1 hands
Player: Joseph Joestar has been kicked out. The winner of this round is Suzumiya Haruhi.
Shuffling the deck
cut at 23
cut at 23
cut at 22
cut at 39
cut at 33
cut at 19
cut at 25
Player: Kujo Jotaro has 4 after 0 hands
Player: Kujo Jotaro has been kicked out. The winner of this round is Suzumiya Haruhi.
Shuffling the deck
cut at 23
cut at 24
cut at 31
cut at 22
cut at 27
cut at 34
cut at 30
Player: Jean Pierre Polnareff has 4 after 0 hands
Player: Jean Pierre Polnareff has been kicked out. The winner of this round is Suzumiya Haruhi.
Shuffling the deck
cut at 24
cut at 21
cut at 33
cut at 39
cut at 27
cut at 20
cut at 21
Player: Kakyoin Noriaki has 4 after 0 hands
Player: Kakyoin Noriaki has been kicked out. The winner of this round is Suzumiya Haruhi.
Shuffling the deck
cut at 19
cut at 22
cut at 32
cut at 13
cut at 30
cut at 28
cut at 14
Player: Mohammed Avdol has 4 after 0 hands
Player: Mohammed Avdol has been kicked out. The winner of this round is Suzumiya Haruhi.
Game over. The winner is SOS Brigade. SOS Brigade got four computers and Stardust Crusaders become an affiliate group of SOS Brigade
